# Ioannis Eleftheriadis

Software Engineer

A highly motivated individual, reliable and responsible person with a work ethic. Competed In various Marital Arts, served in the Cyprus Special Forces. I like the idea of being part of a team that is dedicated to make software products run as smoothly as possible.

ioanniselefth23@gmail.com

99209096

Limassol, Cyprus

#### **EDUCATION**

## **High School Diploma**

St. John High School

09/2015 - 06/2018

Limassol, Cyprus

Ioannina,Greece

## Computer Science And Engineering

University Of Ioannina

09/2019 - 02/2022

Favorite Courses Object Oriented

- Programming(Java)
- Algorithms and Complexity
- Python
- Unix

#### **Computer Science**

Cyprus College - European University

10/2022 - Present

Limassol,Cyprus

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Part time Assistant IT

IT Armor Services Ltd

01/2014 - Present Limassol,Cyprus

Tasks

- Computer Service
- Computer Instalation and Configuration
- Structure Cabling

#### Software Development Internship Soft-Surge LTD

06/2022 - Present

Limassol,Cyprus

Achievements/Tasks

- PHP(Laravel) MVC Architecture
- Various Tasks in HTML/CSS/JS and JQuery
- Git environment
- SQL queries and forms
- Wordpress development
- Implemented a rest api using pipedream and postman

#### **SKILLS**

Python

Algorithm Design & Analysis

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### Academic Projects

- Artificial Intelligence Project: Tic Tac Toe Game in Java
- Software Development: Back End Development in Eclipse

Personal Projects: In the link below you can find all of my personal projects and also every exercise i have done for self-improvement

https://github.com/Ioanniselefth/Personal-Portfolio

## CERTIFICATES

European Computer Driving License (ECDL)

Completed all of the 7 courses

Cisco CCNA Level 1 and Level 2 (10/2016 - 06/2018)

Offered by my High School as part of the Networking class

Programming in Java: A Hands-on Introduction (05/2022)

Offered by Codio through Coursera

Programming in Python: A Hands-on Introduction (05/2022)

Offered by Codio through Coursera

Web Development Foundations Career Path (07/2022)

Codecademy part of the Full Stack Engineer Career Path

Responsive Web Design (07/2022)

FreeCodeCamp

## **LANGUAGES**

English (IGCSE Grade:A)

Greek

Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

### INTERESTS

Working Out

Comedy

Movies

Travelling

Martial Arts